memories follow me left and right I can
feel you over here I can feel you over
here you take up every corner of my mind
what you going to do now ever since the
The Day You Went Away now I don't know
how how to eras your body from out my
brain what you going do now maybe I
should just focus on me instead think
about all the nights we were Tangled Up
in your bed oh no oh no oh no oh no
you're going around in circles got you
stuck up in my head yeah memories follow
me left and right I can feel over here I
can feel over here you take up every
corner of my mind your love stays with
me day and night I can feel over here I
can feel over here you take up every
corner of my mind what you going to do
now ever since the the day you went away
tell me how how much more do I got a
drink for the pain now you the things to
me that I just can't Forget think about
all the nights we were Tangled Up in a
bed oh no oh no oh no oh no you're going
round in circles got you stuck up in my
head yeah memories follow me left and
right I can feel feel over here I can
feel over here you take up every corner
of my mind my life stays when the day
and night I can feel over here I can
feel over here you take up every corner
of my mind what you going do know did
you know you're the one that got away
and even though that are still not okay
did you know that my dreams they're all
the same every every time I close my
eyes memories follow me left and right I
can feel you over here I can feel you
over here you take up every corner of my
mind your love stays with me day and
night I can feel here I can feel here
you take up every corner of my mind you
going I can feel over here I can feel
over here you take up every corner of my
mind what you going to do now